<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Single-cell | Hani Jieun Kim</title>
    <link>https://hanijieunkim.netlify.app/tag/single-cell/</link>
      <atom:link href="https://hanijieunkim.netlify.app/tag/single-cell/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description>Single-cell</description>
    <generator>Source Themes Academic (https://sourcethemes.com/academic/)</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <image>
      <url>https://hanijieunkim.netlify.app/images/icon_hu0b7a4cb9992c9ac0e91bd28ffd38dd00_9727_512x512_fill_lanczos_center_2.png</url>
      <title>Single-cell</title>
      <link>https://hanijieunkim.netlify.app/tag/single-cell/</link>
    </image>
    
    <item>
      <title>CiteFuse</title>
      <link>https://hanijieunkim.netlify.app/project/citefuse/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://hanijieunkim.netlify.app/project/citefuse/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Multi-modal profiling of single cells represents one of the latest technological advancements in molecular biology. Among various single-cell multi-modal strategies, cellular indexing of transcriptomes and epitopes by sequencing (CITE-seq) allows simultaneous quantification of two distinct species: RNA and cell-surface proteins. Here, we introduce CiteFuse, a streamlined package consisting of a suite of tools for doublet detection, modality integration, clustering, differential RNA and protein expression analysis, antibody-derived tag evaluation, ligand–receptor interaction analysis and interactive web-based visualization of CITE-seq data.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We demonstrate the capacity of CiteFuse to integrate the two data modalities and its relative advantage against data generated from single-modality profiling using both simulations and real-world CITE-seq data. Furthermore, we illustrate a novel doublet detection method based on a combined index of cell hashing and transcriptome data. Finally, we demonstrate CiteFuse for predicting ligand–receptor interactions by using multi-modal CITE-seq data. Collectively, we demonstrate the utility and effectiveness of CiteFuse for the integrative analysis of transcriptome and epitope profiles from CITE-seq data.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;CiteFuse is freely available at &lt;a href=&#34;http://shiny.maths.usyd.edu.au/CiteFuse/&#34;&gt;http://shiny.maths.usyd.edu.au/CiteFuse/&lt;/a&gt; as an online web service and at &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/SydneyBioX/CiteFuse/&#34;&gt;https://github.com/SydneyBioX/CiteFuse/&lt;/a&gt; as an R package.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
